(this["webpackJsonpviet-vocabulary-app"]=this["webpackJsonpviet-vocabulary-app"]||[]).push([[0],{16:function(e,a,s){e.exports=s(40)},21:function(e,a,s){},40:function(e,a,s){"use strict";s.r(a);var t=s(0),n=s.n(t),o=s(14),i=s.n(o),r=s(15),c=s(2);function l(e){var a=e.flashcard,s=Object(t.useState)(!1),o=Object(c.a)(s,2),i=o[0],r=o[1],l=Object(t.useState)("initial"),u=Object(c.a)(l,2),d=u[0],p=u[1],m=Object(t.useRef)(),h=Object(t.useRef)();function g(){var e=m.current.getBoundingClientRect().height,a=h.current.getBoundingClientRect().height;p(Math.max(e,a,100))}return Object(t.useEffect)(g,[a.question,a.answer,a.options]),Object(t.useEffect)((function(){return window.addEventListener("resize",g),function(){return window.removeEventListener("resize",g)}}),[]),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"card ".concat(i?"flip":""),style:{height:d},onClick:function(){return r(!i)}},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"front",ref:m},a.question,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"flashcard-options"},a.options.map((function(e){return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"flashcard-option",key:e},e)})))),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"back",ref:h},a.answer))}function u(e){var a=e.flashcards;return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"card-grid"},a.map((function(e){return n.a.createElement(l,{flashcard:e,key:e.id})})))}s(21),s(22);var d=["go ( hang out \u0111i ch\u01a1i )","do","work","learn/ study","answer","ask ( c\xe2u h\u1ecfi question)","play ( tr\xf2 ch\u01a1i game)","need","want/would like","take","give","like","come to","visit","see","look ( t\xf4i nh\xecn th\u1ea5y) i see","understand","open","close","know","find","love","(b\u1ecf) leave","think","to rest / break time","buy","sell","eat","drink","take","help","have","miss","remember to","waiting for","move","help","stand up","sit down","lay down","sleep","stupid (adjective)","meet","run","walk","hear","read","speak / say","write","send","stop","turn on","turn off","receive","decide","marry","divorce","angry","to plan","laugh","cry","smile","to finish/end","start/begin","live","die","draw","sing","dance","shower","pee (acceptable only for babies)","poop ( c\u1ee9t shit - noun)","busy","prepare","repeat","remind","cancel","booking","call","return","brush teeth","hit/ fight","to punch","wash","wash hair","wash clothes","watch","use","slap","touch","wake up","to joke","take hand","feel","propose","kiss","hug","come back","to go away (c\xfat \u0111i -never come back)","talking/ chatting","texting"],p=[{question:"\ufeff\u0111i",answer:"go ( hang out \u0111i ch\u01a1i )",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["learn / study","understand","to plan"],id:6922035156},{question:"l\xe0m",answer:"do",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["read","wash clothes","move"],id:7842813235},{question:"l\xe0m vi\u1ec7c",answer:"work",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["understand","turn off","hear"],id:6488324518},{question:"h\u1ecdc",answer:"learn / study",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["touch","touch","wash clothes"],id:2920489179},{question:"tr\u1ea3 l\u1eddi",answer:"answer",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["close","booking","hug"],id:6167944084},{question:"h\u1ecfi",answer:"ask ( c\xe2u h\u1ecfi question)",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["run","sell","to punch"],id:4740347391},{question:"ch\u01a1i",answer:"play ( tr\xf2 ch\u01a1i game)",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["have","give","visit"],id:1609980463},{question:"c\u1ea7n",answer:"need",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["stop","visit","to finish / end"],id:2569281542},{question:"mu\u1ed1n",answer:"want / would like",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["start / begin","call","run"],id:2579154948},{question:"l\u1ea5y",answer:"take",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["look ( t\xf4i nh\xecn th\u1ea5y) i see","come back","shower"],id:1213035853},{question:"cho",answer:"give",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["need","kiss","propose"],id:7143517035},{question:"th\xedch",answer:"like",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["use","divorce","start / begin"],id:7660116651},{question:"\u0111\u1ebfn",answer:"come to",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["slap","to plan","move"],id:2933438296},{question:"th\u0103m",answer:"visit",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["to joke","kiss","start / begin"],id:8459421546},{question:"th\u1ea5y",answer:"see",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["do","to joke","laugh"],id:7839430993},{question:"nh\xecn",answer:"look ( t\xf4i nh\xecn th\u1ea5y) i see",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["divorce","slap","to rest / break time"],id:6586968172},{question:"hi\u1ec3u",answer:"understand",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["hug","kiss","prepare"],id:5219276581},{question:"m\u1edf",answer:"open",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["meet","watch","to finish / end"],id:8376166747},{question:"\u0111\xf3ng",answer:"close",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["take","to rest / break time","miss"],id:4697267829},{question:"bi\u1ebft",answer:"know",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["shower","busy","turn off"],id:8838158599},{question:"t\xecm",answer:"find",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["stand up","go ( hang out \u0111i ch\u01a1i )","cry"],id:2564122546},{question:"y\xeau",answer:"love",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["sleep","take","brush teeth"],id:7457605980},{question:"r\u1eddi kh\u1ecfi",answer:"(b\u1ecf) leave",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["take","help","sing"],id:1535658748},{question:"ngh\u0129",answer:"think",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["meet","return","read"],id:9659912052},{question:"ngh\u1ec9",answer:"to rest / break time",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["poop ( c\u1ee9t shit - noun)","brush teeth","poop ( c\u1ee9t shit - noun)"],id:4238472069},{question:"mua",answer:"buy",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["learn / study","wash","poop ( c\u1ee9t shit - noun)"],id:2310417992},{question:"b\xe1n",answer:"sell",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["sleep","propose","do"],id:7078305758},{question:"\u0103n",answer:"eat",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["to rest / break time","meet","send"],id:1878481412},{question:"u\u1ed1ng",answer:"drink",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["like","touch","visit"],id:6865667284},{question:"c\u1ea7m",answer:"take",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["start / begin","start / begin","hear"],id:7991966545},{question:"gi\xfap",answer:"help",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["to plan","slap","move"],id:2937860216},{question:"c\xf3",answer:"have",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["turn off","slap","use"],id:5201541467},{question:"nh\u1edb ( nh\u1edb nhung)",answer:"miss",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["live","booking","write"],id:1979305649},{question:"ghi nh\u1edb",answer:"remember to",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["sing","live","sit down"],id:9406775611},{question:"ch\u1edd \u0111\u1ee3i",answer:"waiting for",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["drink","take hand","to punch"],id:3159340765},{question:"di chuy\u1ec3n",answer:"move",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["waiting for","close","to punch"],id:8808091711},{question:"gi\xfap \u0111\u1ee1",answer:"help",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["understand","sing","sleep"],id:2106274552},{question:"\u0111\u1ee9ng",answer:"stand up",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["need","miss","waiting for"],id:7300062361},{question:"ng\u1ed3i",answer:"sit down",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["know","come back","laugh"],id:3489360652},{question:"n\u1eb1m",answer:"lay down",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["(b\u1ecf) leave","return","poop ( c\u1ee9t shit - noun)"],id:9459847012},{question:"ng\u1ee7",answer:"sleep",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["sing","wake up","live"],id:1700465073},{question:"ngu",answer:"stupid (adjective)",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["cancel","remind","drink"],id:3187417889},{question:"g\u1eb7p",answer:"meet",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["remember to","sleep","give"],id:3539971185},{question:"ch\u1ea1y",answer:"run",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["remind","wash clothes","smile"],id:1627533644},{question:"\u0111i b\u1ed9",answer:"walk",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["drink","walk","to punch"],id:7013297348},{question:"nghe",answer:"hear",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["divorce","have","draw"],id:7514557419},{question:"\u0111\u1ecdc",answer:"read",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["slap","(b\u1ecf) leave","decide"],id:5641405956},{question:"n\xf3i",answer:"speak / say",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["understand","take","wash hair"],id:5544312148},{question:"vi\u1ebft",answer:"write",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["cry","to plan","dance"],id:8821475189},{question:"g\u1eedi",answer:"send",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["decide","cancel","stand up"],id:5022671681},{question:"d\u1eebng l\u1ea1i",answer:"stop",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["to punch","open","draw"],id:3528586867},{question:"b\u1eadt",answer:"turn on",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["laugh","think","help"],id:5180483502},{question:"t\u1eaft",answer:"turn off",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["wash hair","play ( tr\xf2 ch\u01a1i game)","texting"],id:6238013479},{question:"nh\u1eadn",answer:"receive",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["have","stupid (adjective)","need"],id:5140492644},{question:"quy\u1ebft \u0111\u1ecbnh",answer:"decide",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["go ( hang out \u0111i ch\u01a1i )","turn on","stand up"],id:9788169271},{question:"c\u01b0\u1edbi",answer:"marry",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["think","die","close"],id:9847213128},{question:"ly h\xf4n",answer:"divorce",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["stupid (adjective)","lay down","cry"],id:5898421728},{question:"t\u1ee9c gi\u1eadn",answer:"angry",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["sing","meet","receive"],id:9658876109},{question:"l\xean k\u1ebf ho\u1ea1ch",answer:"to plan",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["booking","live","to go away (c\xfat \u0111i -never come back)"],id:7659689672},{question:"c\u01b0\u1eddi",answer:"laugh",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["see","busy","help"],id:8853711713},{question:"kh\xf3c",answer:"cry",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["move","die","come to"],id:6456802014},{question:"m\u1ec9m c\u01b0\u1eddi",answer:"smile",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["sing","send","hit / fight"],id:6323686250},{question:"k\u1ebft th\xfac",answer:"to finish / end",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["do","wash hair","find"],id:2675972177},{question:"b\u1eaft \u0111\u1ea7u",answer:"start / begin",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["wake up","smile","sleep"],id:3566322195},{question:"s\u1ed1ng",answer:"live",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["write","to joke","wash hair"],id:1321286030},{question:"ch\u1ebft",answer:"die",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["die","understand","repeat"],id:8789071858},{question:"v\u1ebd",answer:"draw",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["speak / say","waiting for","understand"],id:5073243500},{question:"h\xe1t",answer:"sing",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["find","return","help"],id:3928886106},{question:"nh\u1ea3y",answer:"dance",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["prepare","busy","to plan"],id:8307956541},{question:"t\u1eafm",answer:"shower",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["eat","die","meet"],id:3445167008},{question:"\u0111i \u0111\xe1i",answer:"pee (acceptable only for babies)",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["hug","lay down","pee (acceptable only for babies)"],id:2360241045},{question:"\u0111i \u1ecb ( \u1ec9a)",answer:"poop ( c\u1ee9t shit - noun)",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["take","receive","wash"],id:5949861947},{question:"b\u1eadn",answer:"busy",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["cancel","help","draw"],id:5712072669},{question:"chu\u1ea9n b\u1ecb",answer:"prepare",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["help","give","lay down"],id:5170397547},{question:"nh\u1eafc l\u1ea1i",answer:"repeat",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["laugh","hug","have"],id:6813552721},{question:"nh\u1eafc nh\u1edf ( ng\u1ee3i nh\u1edb)",answer:"remind",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["decide","to rest / break time","to rest / break time"],id:1824453445},{question:"h\u1ee7y",answer:"cancel",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["turn on","visit","drink"],id:1559407769},{question:"\u0111\u1eb7t",answer:"booking",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["stand up","drink","slap"],id:9188262470},{question:"g\u1ecdi",answer:"call",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["to plan","texting","watch"],id:7157237909},{question:"tr\u1edf l\u1ea1i",answer:"return",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["use","busy","die"],id:5667363612},{question:"\u0111\xe1nh r\u0103ng",answer:"brush teeth",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["die","speak / say","hug"],id:3322638055},{question:"\u0111\xe1nh / \u0111\xe1nh nhau",answer:"hit / fight",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["run","slap","pee (acceptable only for babies)"],id:5288514424},{question:"\u0111\u1ea5m",answer:"to punch",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["answer","give","meet"],id:7460290792},{question:"r\u1eeda",answer:"wash",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["shower","pee (acceptable only for babies)","help"],id:9405346548},{question:"g\u1ed9i \u0111\u1ea7u",answer:"wash hair",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["wake up","buy","do"],id:1774333156},{question:"gi\u1eb7t qu\u1ea7n \xe1o",answer:"wash clothes",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["help","want / would like","to plan"],id:4784134436},{question:"xem",answer:"watch",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["hit / fight","decide","miss"],id:9060006292},{question:"s\u1eed d\u1ee5ng",answer:"use",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["understand","draw","love"],id:2368068530},{question:"t\xe1t",answer:"slap",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["wash clothes","come to","draw"],id:3979200537},{question:"s\u1edd",answer:"touch",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["feel","meet","turn on"],id:8876369730},{question:"th\u1ee9c d\u1eady",answer:"wake up",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["busy","to go away (c\xfat \u0111i -never come back)","stupid (adjective)"],id:4565677673},{question:"\u0111\xf9a",answer:"to joke",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["close","call","lay down"],id:3240271217},{question:"c\u1ea7m tay",answer:"take hand",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["wash","sit down","close"],id:9342941648},{question:"c\u1ea3m th\u1ea5y",answer:"feel",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["buy","cry","poop ( c\u1ee9t shit - noun)"],id:2879796398},{question:"c\u1ea7u h\xf4n",answer:"propose",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["speak / say","laugh","talking / chatting"],id:2131557145},{question:"h\xf4n",answer:"kiss",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["laugh","send","start / begin"],id:1368048878},{question:"\xf4m",answer:"hug",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["remind","pee (acceptable only for babies)","to punch"],id:9165422501},{question:"tr\u1edf v\u1ec1",answer:"come back",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["watch","help","visit"],id:5653923137},{question:"\u0111i \u0111i",answer:"to go away (c\xfat \u0111i -never come back)",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["like","draw","wash hair"],id:9309576639},{question:"tr\xf2 chuy\u1ec7n",answer:"talking / chatting",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["marry","take","call"],id:9727028625},{question:"nh\u1eafn tin",answer:"texting",category:"Vietnamese Class Vocab 3",options:["want / would like","sleep","have"],id:8168099251}];var m=function(){var e=Object(t.useState)([]),a=Object(c.a)(e,2),s=a[0],o=a[1],i=Object(t.useState)([]),l=Object(c.a)(i,2),m=(l[0],l[1],p.length),h=(Object(t.useRef)(),Object(t.useRef)());function g(e){var a=document.createElement("textarea");return a.innerHTML=e,a.value}return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("form",{className:"header",onSubmit:function(e){e.preventDefault();var a=p.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()}));o(a.slice(0,h.current.value).map((function(e,a){var s,t,n=g(e.answer),o=(s=d.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})),t=n,s.filter((function(e){return e!=t}))),i=[].concat(Object(r.a)(o.slice(0,3)),[n]);return{id:"".concat(a,"-").concat(Date.now()),question:g(e.question),answer:n,options:i.sort((function(){return Math.random()-.5}))}})))}},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"form-group"},n.a.createElement("label",{htmlFor:"amount"},"Number of Words"),n.a.createElement("input",{type:"number",id:"amount",min:"1",step:"1",defaultValue:m,ref:h})),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"form-group"},n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn"},"Generate"))),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},n.a.createElement(u,{flashcards:s})))};i.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(m,null)),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[16,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.ae66df5f.chunk.js.map